getprofitadz.com 2016-03-20

# getprofitadz.com Privacy Policy

getprofitadz.com Privacy Policy
This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally
identifiable information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is
information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person,
or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how
we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our
website.
What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address,
mailing address, phone number or other details to help you with your experience.
When do we collect information?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, fill out a form or enter information on our site.
How do we use your information?
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter,
respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the
following ways:
    • To personalize user's experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product
      offerings in which you are most interested.
    • To improve our website in order to better serve you.
    • To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
    • To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
    • To quickly process your transactions.
    • To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.
How do we protect visitor information?
We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.
We use regular Malware Scanning. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only
accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to
keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure
Socket Layer (SSL) technology. We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters,
submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information. All transactions are
processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.
Do we use 'cookies'?
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your
Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and
capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the
items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or
current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us
compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and
tools in the future.
We use cookies to:
    • Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart.
    • Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.
    • Keep track of advertisements.
    • Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and
tools in the future. We may also use trusted third party services that track this information on our behalf.
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off
all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so
look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If users disable cookies in their browser:
If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled It will turn off some of the features that make your site
experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place orders.
Third Party Disclosure
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we
provide you with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us
in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this
information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply
with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-
personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other
uses.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These
third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability
for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and
welcome any feedback about these sites.
Google
Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to
provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en
We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on
our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and
other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content
network privacy policy.
We have implemented the following:
    • Google Display Network Impression Reporting
    • Demographics and Interests Reporting
We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies)
and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data
regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.
Opting out:
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you
can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics
Opt Out Browser add on.
California Online Privacy Protection Act
CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy
policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and
conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California
consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and
those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. - See more at:
http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf
According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:
Users can visit our site anonymously. Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page,
or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website. Our Privacy Policy link includes the word
'Privacy', and can be easily be found on the page specified above.
Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:
    • On our Privacy Policy Page

Users are able to change their personal information:
     • By logging in to their account
     • By chatting with us or sending us a ticket
How does our site handle do not track signals?
We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT)
browser mechanism is in place.
Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking?
It's also important to note that we do not allow third party behavioral tracking
COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)
When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children's Online Privacy
Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation's consumer protection
agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to
protect children's privacy and safety online.
We do not specifically market to children under 13.
Fair Information Practices
The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts
they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe.
Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply
with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.
In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data
breach occur:
We will notify the users via email
     • Within 7 business days
We will notify the users via in site notification
     • Within 7 business days
We also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally
enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not
only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts
or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.
CAN SPAM Act
The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial
messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough
penalties for violations.
We collect your email address in order to:
To be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at
and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
getprofitadz.com
JL Gatot Subroto
Timur No 178
Denpasar-Bali
Indonesia
ivankaweono@gmail.com
